<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".DocsActivity">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="409dp"
        android:layout_height="729dp"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteX="1dp"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteY="1dp">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:text="  RULES FOR RENTAL BIKE RENTAL The Regulations define the rules of use, conditions, scope of rights and responsibilities of persons using Mountain Bike Rentals   § 1 General Provisions 1. Bicycles are the property of EcoRiders Sp. z o. o. with its registered office in Bielsko-Biała (43-300), ul. Żywiecka 92/4, entered in the Register of Entrepreneurs kept by the District Court in Bielsko-Biała, VIII Commercial Department of the National Court Register under KRS number: 0000791039, NIP 9372722119 (&quot;ECORIDERS&quot;, &quot;Owner&quot;). 2. The rental service is open from May 1 to October 31, seven days a week from Monday to Friday from 10:00 to 19:00 and on weekends from 9:00 to 19:00. 3. Rented bikes are technically sound and should be returned to the Rental Office in the same condition. 4. An integral part of the Regulations is the price list of bicycles available on the ECORIDERS website: http://endurotrails.pl/. 5. The Lessee is personally responsible for rented bikes. 6. Each person of legal age concludes a contract for the bike they will use. One adult can rent only one bicycle for their own use. It is forbidden to rent bicycles by adults of the designation for use by other adults. 7. It is allowed to rent bikes by adults for minors (children) under their care. In the case of renting bicycles for minors (children), it is agreed that one adult may rent a maximum of two bikes intended for use by minors (children) under his care. If there are two guardians (adults), they may rent a total of up to three bikes for use by minors (children) under their care, the Lessee undertakes to provide the year of birth of minors (children) using the rented bikes so that the Rental can verify whether the users will not be too young. 8. An underage person may use the bike only in the presence of an adult - the Lessee who takes full responsibility for the rented bike and the person using it. 9. Contact with the Rental Office at the following e-mail address: info@endurotrails.pl or telephone number 698205786 10. If the word bicycle is used, bikes rented by the Lessee shall also be understood.  § 2 RENTER 1. The bike may be rented only by an adult who has full legal capacity (&quot;the Lessee&quot;). 2. To rent a bike, the person indicated in paragraph 1 is obliged to: a) read the content of these Regulations and accept its content, b) sign a contract with ECORIDERS at the Rental Office and c) pay in advance the fee for renting a bike according to current price list available on the website. 3. The Lessee undertakes to: a) comply with these Regulations, the Agreement and the regulations of mountain bike paths b) using the rented bike for its intended purpose, c) timely return of the bike to the Rental, d) immediately inform the Rental Company employee of any problems with the bike, e) refrain from self-repair of the rented bike, f) cover any repairs of the bike arising from the sole intentional fault of the Lessee (or persons using the bikes under his care), g) maintaining sobriety while using the bicycle 4. ECORIDERS reserves the right to verify the Lessee's sobriety. 5. The Lessee is prohibited from renting or renting a bike to third parties, except for minors, using bicycles under his care in accordance with § 1 of the Regulations. 6. The Lessee may not pose a threat to his or her life or health of other people using mountain bike routes. 7. In the event of loss or destruction of the rented bike / bikes or parts of equipment as a result of circumstances for which the Renter is responsible, the Renter undertakes to reimburse the equivalent of the costs corresponding to the value of the bike and its equipment. 8. Not giving up the bike after 2 hours from the deadline and not informing the Rental about the reason for the delay will be considered as misappropriation of the bike and reported to law enforcement authorities. In addition, a contractual penalty of PLN 5,000.00 will be imposed on the Lessee. ECORIDERS may claim compensation from the Lessee on general terms. 9. The Lessee bears full responsibility for accidents, all damages caused while using the bicycle. The Lessee, being a participant in mountain bike paths, is obliged to follow the rules of traveling along designated routes and does so only at his own risk. 10. The Lessee is solely responsible for any damage caused to third parties.  § 3 Renting and booking of bicycles. Withdrawal and resignation. 1. Bikes can be rented in person at the Rental Office, by e-mail (info@endurotrails.pl) or via the website http://endurotrails.pl/ 2. Upon signing the contract, the Lessee concludes a civil law contract in accordance with the conditions set out in the content of the contract and in these Regulations. 3. The contract is concluded when the contract is signed at the Rental, after having read and accepted these Regulations and paying the amount for renting a bike. 4. In the event of making an earlier reservation, after obtaining confirmation of the bike's availability within the period specified by the Lessee, the Lessee must pay the amount for a Giant Reign 27.5 PLN 2 170 PLN, for a Giant Reign 29 PLN 2 170 PLN, for a Giant Reign 29 SX PLN 190, for Giant Trance 27.5 bike PLN 2 170 PLN, for Giant Trance 29 PLN 2 170 PLN, for Liv Hail bike PLN 170, for Giant Reign E + 2 bike PLN 250 to finalize the reservation. 5. The Lessee has the right to resign from renting a bike provided that the Rental is notified of this fact by e-mail at the latest 3 days before the agreed date of conclusion of the contract. In such a situation, the Rental Company will refund the Lessee the reservation fee paid (down payment), within 14 days of receipt of the resignation statement, to the account indicated by the Tenant in the resignation statement. 6. In the event of resignation from the conclusion of the rental contract less than 3 days before the planned date of starting the rental of the bike, the reservation fee (deposit) will not be refundable. Not accepting the reserved bike on the agreed date is also considered as tantamount to resignation from the conclusion of the lease agreement. 7. The remuneration for renting a bike (according to the Price List available on the Rental's website) is collected in advance at the time of transferring the bike to the Lessee. 8. In the event of payment of the reservation fee (down payment) at the time of booking, this amount at the time of signing the contract will be credited to the Rental fee for renting a bike. 9. In case of doubt, in the case of renting a bike via e-mail or the form available on the website, the reservation fee paid by the Lessee is a down payment in accordance with the provisions of the Civil Code. 10. The Rental reserves the right to refuse to sign a contract and rent a bike if it raises doubts about the tenant's sobriety or being the Lessee under the influence of drugs or willingness to rent a bike for sublease or lending to third parties. 11. The Rental reserves the right to transfer the reservation to another bike of the same class without informing the Lessee of this fact.  § 4 Rules for booking bikes via the website  1. Bicycle bookings can be made via the website http://endurotrails.pl/ 2. The Lessee makes the reservation by following the instructions appearing on the website. 3. The condition for successful booking of a Bike is that the Rental Company receives from the Payment Operator (transfers24) confirmation of the availability of funds necessary to pay the Prepayment to the Bike rental contract. 4. The Rental reserves that the process of obtaining confirmation referred to in para. 3 above may last up to a maximum of 60 minutes from the moment of placing the order to the payment operator, transferring funds to cover the deposit for the rental of the Bike. 5. The Rental Office will immediately, after receiving from the Payment Operator confirmation of the availability of funds necessary to complete the transaction, send the Tenant to the e-mail address provided information confirming the reservation of the selected Bike. 6. If the Rental does not receive confirmation of the availability of funds necessary to pay the Deposit from the Payment Operator within 60 minutes or if it receives information about the lack of availability of funds necessary to make the transaction, the Rental will inform the Buyer that the transaction cannot be completed and the Bicycle reservation stops effective if the Rental does not receive the Deposit (reservation fee) within 60 minutes of receiving the indicated message.  § 5 Complaints  1. Complaints with a detailed description of the situation should be reported to ECORIDERS via e-mail to the following address: info@endurotrails.pl 2. The complaint will be considered within 14 days of receipt of the notification.  § 6 Protection of personal data 1. The administrator of personal data of Participants, Reporters and guardians is EcoRiders Sp. z o. o. with its registered office in Bielsko-Biała (43-300), ul. Żywiecka 92/4, entered into the Register of Entrepreneurs kept by the District Court in Bielsko-Biała, VIII Commercial Department of the National Court Register under KRS number: 0000791039, NIP 9372722119 (&quot;Administrator&quot;). 2. In matters related to the processing of personal data, you can contact us at: info@endurotrails.pl or at: address ul. Żywiecka 92/4, 43-300 Bielsko-Biała with the note &quot;RODO&quot; 3. [The purposes of data processing] Your personal data will be processed: (i) for the purposes necessary to perform the contract concluded by you with the Administrator; (ii) for the purposes necessary to fulfill the legal obligations incumbent on the Administrator, in particular those arising from tax law and accounting regulations; (iii) for purposes resulting from legitimate interests pursued by the Administrator, in particular providing contact with you before the conclusion of the contract and during the contract period and to establish, investigate or defend against any claims. 4. [Basics of data processing] The grounds for processing your personal data are: (i) art. 6 clause 1 lit. b) Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46 / EC (General Data Protection Regulation ), hereinafter referred to as: &quot;GDPR&quot;; (ii) art. 6 clause 1 lit. c) GDPR; (iii) art. 6 clause 1 lit. f) GDPR. 5. [Recipients of personal data] The recipients of your personal data may be - only in cases where it is necessary and to the extent necessary - entities cooperating with the Administrator in the scope of services provided to the Administrator and supporting the Administrator's current business processes, in particular entities providing services IT, marketing, legal, courier, banks. 6. [Period of personal data processing] Your personal data will be processed for the duration of the contract concluded with the Administrator, and after this period for the period of limitation of any claims resulting from generally applicable law. If the processing is necessary to fulfill the legal obligation incumbent on the Administrator, your personal data will be processed for a period of time resulting from the generally applicable provisions of law, in particular the provisions of tax law and accounting regulations. If the processing is necessary for the purposes of legitimate interests pursued by the Administrator or by a third party, then your personal data will be processed for no longer than necessary for the purposes for which the data are processed or until you object to the processing personal data. 7. [Permissions] In connection with the conclusion of the contract with the Administrator, you have the right to: (i) access to your personal data, (ii) rectify personal data, (iii) delete personal data, (iv) limit the processing of personal data , (v) transferring data, including the right to receive data and send it to another administrator or to request, if technically possible, to send this data directly to another administrator, (vi) to object to the processing of personal data, (vii) to lodge a complaint to the authority Supervisory Board in the field of personal data protection. 8. [Voluntary provision of data] Providing personal data by you is voluntary, but necessary to conclude an agreement with the Administrator, and necessary to ensure contact and proper performance of the agreement concluded with the Administrator. 9. [Source of data] Your data was obtained in connection with the conclusion of the contract with the Administrator for the purposes necessary for the proper implementation of this contract.  § 7 Final provisions 1. The Rental Regulations are available on the ECORIDERS website. 2. In matters not covered by these regulations, the provisions of the Civil Code shall apply. " />
    </ScrollView>
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>